Tyler McNiff



tylermcguy@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/tyler-mcniff

https://crazy-dev-hero.netlify.app/

Summary

@crazydevhero

Software engineer with 10+ years experience spread across of multiple programming languages and technologies especially Blockchain & DevOps.

Always eager to learn new things and look for new challenges

Happy to work independently or in a close team environment, and apply a positive attitude to every task undertaken.

Experience working with projects with high traffic volumes.

√# Top quality Smart Contract Creator/Security Auditor.

√# High-load back-end C/C++/Node.js/Python developer.

Here's my

GitHub: https://www.github.com/crazydevhero Website: https://crazy-dev-hero.netlify.app/ Telegram: https://t.me/crazydevhero

Experience



υρ Blockchain Developer

Upwork

May 2022 - Present (2 months +)

From what I've gathered/heard, freelancing was another big source of income.

It has its own pros/cons compared to regular jobs.

I'm adding all my projects on my portfolio website.

🌈 Blockchain Developer

Trillest Group

Aug 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

Responsible for handling blockchain-related projects with other developers.

My last project is TRILLEST with the same name as the company.

I appreciate my experience here that let me leverage my existing knowledge about blockchain.



Senior Developer

Hidden Brains InfoTech Pvt. Ltd.

Jun 2018 - Jul 2020 (2 years 2 months)

I was responsible for managing a team of nearly 10 developers.

The company had a long track record since 2003 and I really loved their work culture there.

I mainly worked on Web/Mobile projects as a senior developer.

Full Stack Developer

Pineapple Workshop

Jul 2016 - Jun 2018 (2 years)

This was my first experience in the Software Development field.

I worked as a full-stack developer on several projects

RentRoom (http://getrentroom.com/)

Quiker (https://quikerco.com/)

Memo Maker (https://memomaker.app/)

Education



Cornell University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Sep 2013 - May 2016

Licenses & Certifications

- Blockchain Basics Great Learning **COLIABEY**
- Algorithm in C Great Learning **WEMWGWTB**
- Blockchain Process Great Learning **DVMXYHLP**
- GO Programming Language Great Learning **AQSBKXQO**
- Python Practice Codes Great Learning **KVFDKCUK**
- React JS Great Learning YLJKGBKV
- Solidity codedamn 03d46fa98a6b1425e1e9d885328ba90e93fe2e63

Skills

ethers.js • Blockchain • Smart Contracts • Hardhat • Solidity • Decentralized Applications (DApps) • web3.js • Ethereum • EVM • C++